Almost all of us have them in our body, they accumulate throughout our lives and they may be causing serious health conditions.
我们几乎所有人的体内都有它们，它们在我们的整个生命中不断积累，并且可能正在导致严重的健康问题。
They've been called 'forever chemicals', but what are they, where do they come from, and what can we do about them?
它们被称为"永久化学品"，但它们是什么，从哪里来，我们又该如何应对呢？
'Forever chemicals' take their name from the fact that they contain fluorine-carbon bonds, and because they last, if not forever, for a very long time.
"永久化学品"得名于它们含有氟碳键，而且它们能持续存在——即使不是永远，也是极其漫长的时间。
These chemical bonds are incredibly difficult to break down, which means that contaminants from these chemicals build up over time in our environment.
这些化学键非常难以分解，这意味着这些化学物质产生的污染物会随着时间的推移在我们的环境中不断积累。
As well as in our bodies, they've been found in the soil and in drinking water.
除了在我们的身体里，它们还存在于土壤和饮用水中。
While some have now been banned, these chemicals have been used in a wide range of consumer products.
虽然其中一些现在已被禁止，但这些化学品已被广泛应用于各种消费品中。
They have a repellent effect on oil and water and so have been used for stain-proofing furniture and carpets.
它们对油和水具有排斥作用，因此被用于防污家具和地毯。
Forever chemicals have been used to make non-stick pans and grease-proof food packaging.
永久化学品曾被用于制造不粘锅和防油食品包装。
You can find them in waterproof clothing and bicycle lubricants.
你可以在防水服装和自行车润滑油中找到它们。
Particular concern has been raised about their use in cosmetics and other personal care products.
它们在化妆品和其他个人护理产品中的使用引发了特别关注。
These products are often used near mucous membranes, like those in our eyes and mouths, which could make it easier for chemicals to be absorbed into our bodies.
这些产品通常用在黏膜附近，比如我们眼睛和嘴巴周围的黏膜，这可能使化学物质更容易被吸收到我们的体内。
The exact level of risk is uncertain, but studies have suggested links between these compounds and conditions such as cancer, reproduction problems, developmental problems in children, and reduced immunity to disease.
确切的风险水平尚不确定，但研究表明这些化合物与癌症、生殖问题、儿童发育问题以及疾病免疫力下降等状况存在关联。
However, the level of exposure at which people become at risk is not yet clear.
然而，人们暴露于危险的具体程度尚不清楚。
It may be impossible to completely avoid these chemicals, but people can take steps to reduce their exposure.
完全避免这些化学物质几乎是不可能的，但人们可以采取措施减少接触到这些物质。
Air and water filters, as well as reducing the amount of dust in our living spaces is one way to do this.
空气和水过滤器，以及减少生活空间中的灰尘量，是其中一种方法。
Another way is to carefully check the ingredients of cosmetics as well as the materials in carpets and furniture before buying them.
另一种方法是在购买前仔细检查化妆品的成分以及地毯和家具的原料。